A Guide to the Office of the Vice-President, Louis A. Pardue Records, 1950-1963
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Board of Visitors Resolutions, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 664)
- Business Manager-Cassell, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 665)
- C, General, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 666)
- Ceramic Engineering-Dear, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 667)
- Chemistry-Krug, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 668)
- Civil Engineering-Morris, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 669)
- Commission on Graduate Education in the Agricultural Sciences, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 670)
- Conference of Deans of Southern Graduate Schools (3 folders), 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 671a-c)
- Continuing Education Center at VPI, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 672)
- Cooperative Engineering-Cain, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 673)
- Council of the Southern Mountains, Inc., 1960 (Box 16, Folder 674)
- D, General, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 675)
- Dairy Science-Graf, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 676)
- Danville Branch-Taylor, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 677)
- Dedication of Reactor, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 678)
- Electrical Engineering-Powley, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 679)
- Engineering and Architecture-Whittemore, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 680)
- English and Foreign Languages-Harrison, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 681)
- Entomology-Grayson, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 682)
- F, General, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 683)
- Faculty Applications, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 684)
- Faculty Appointments, Agriculture, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 685)
- Faculty Appointments, Applied Science and Business Administration, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 686)
- Faculty Appointments, Engineering and Architecture, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 687)
- Faculty Committees, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 688)
- Faculty Letters to Dr. Furr, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 689)
- Faculty Library, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 690)
- Faculty Promotions (3 folders), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 691a-c)
- Faculty Resignations, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 692)
- Faculty Retirements, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 693)
- Faculty Tenure, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 694)
- Ford Foundation (3 folders), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 695a-c)
- Foreign Students, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 696)
- French Exhibit, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 697)
- Forestry and Wildlife, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 698)
- G, General, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 699)
- Geological Sciences-Cooper, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 700)
- Graduate Fellowships, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 701)
- H, General, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 702)
- Health, Education, and Welfare, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 703a-b)
- Home Economics-Harper, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 704)
- Horticulture-Judkins, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 705)
- Industrial Engineering-Manning, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 706)
- Institute for International Education, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 707)
- Insurance Letter for Faculty, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 708)
- Insurance Letter for Graduate Students, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 709)
- Invitations, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 710)
- Junior Academy of Science, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 711)
- K, General, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 712)
- L, General, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 713)
- Langley Field, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 714)
- Letters of Recommendation, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 715)
- M, General, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 716)
- Mathematics-Hatcher, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 717)
- Metallurgical Engineering-Eckel, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 718)
- Military-Devine, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 719)
- N, General, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 720)
- National Science Foundation (3 folders), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 721a-c)
- O, General, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 722)
- P, General, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 723)
- Personnel-Evans, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 724)
- Philosophy and Religion-Grover, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 725)
- Physics-Gilmer, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 726)
- Plant Pathology and Physiology-Wingard, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 727)
- President-Newman, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 728)
- Public Relations-McNeil, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 729)
- Poultry Husbandry-Howes, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 730)
- Questionnaires (5 folders), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 731a-e)
- R, General, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 732)
- Radford College-Martin, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 733)
- Regional Advisory Council on Nuclear Energy, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 734)
- Registrar-Slusher, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 735)
- ROTC Program, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 736)
- Rural Sociology-Tate, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 737)
- S, General, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 738)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 739)
- Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 740)
- Southern Interstate Compact on Nuclear Development, 1957-1960 (Box 17, Folder 741)
- Southern Regional Education Board, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 742)
- Speeches, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 743)
- State Board of Education, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 744)
- State Council on Higher Education, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 745)
- State Fair Committee, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 746)
- Statistics-Harshbarger, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 747)
- Student Activities Committee, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 748)
- Student Affairs Physical Location, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 749a-b)
- Student Correspondence-Graduate Students, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 750)
- Student Correspondence-Undergraduates, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 751)
- Summer School, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 752)
- T, General, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 753)
- University Club, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 754)
- Virginia Academy of Science, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 755)
- Virginia Education Association, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 756)
- VPI Educational Foundation-Hutcheson, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 757)
- Vocational Education-Sanders, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 758)
- Washington, D.C., 1960 (Box 18, Folder 759)
- A, General, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 760)
- Academic Council, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 761)
- Accreditation, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 762)
- Admissions-Farrier, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 763)
- Aeronautical Engineering-Truitt, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 764)
- Agriculture-Dietrick (2 folders), 1961 (Box 18, Folder 765a-b)
- Agricultural Economics-Tate, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 766)
- Agricultural Engineering-Swink, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 767)
- Agricultural Experiment Station-Young, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 768)
- Agricultural Extension Service, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 769)
- Agronomy-Dunton, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 770)
- Alumni Association, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 771)
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 772)
- American Association of University Professors, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 773)
- American Council on Education, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 774)
- Animal Husbandry-Litton, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 775)
- Annual Reports (2 folders), 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 776a-b)
- Applied Science and Business Administration-Johnston, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 777)
- Architecture-Currie (2 folders), 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 778a-b)
- Association of Graduate Studies, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 779)
- Association of Virginia Colleges, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 780)
- Athletic Council, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 781)
- Atomic Energy Commission, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 782)
- B, General, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 783)
- Biology-Orcutt, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 784)
- Board Resolutions, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 785)
- Business Manager-Cassell, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 786)
- C, General, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 787)
- Capital Outlay Commission, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 788)
- Chemical Engineering-Bull, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 789)
- Chemistry-Krug, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 790)
- Civil Engineering-Morris, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 791)
- Commencement, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 792)
- Conference of Southern Graduate Deans (3 folders), 1961 (Box 18, Folder 793a-c)
- Council on American Graduate Schools, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 794)
- Council of Graduate Schools in the United States, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 795)
- Council of State College Presidents, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 796)
- D, General, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 797)
- Dairy Science-Graf, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 798)
- Danville Branch-Taylor, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 799)
- Director of Development-Fisher (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 800a-b)
- E, General, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 801)
- Educational Foundation-Hutcheson, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 802)
- Electrical Engineering-Powley, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 803)
- Engineering and Architecture-Whittemore, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 804)
- Engineering Mechanics-Pletta, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 805)
- English and Foreign Languages-Peacock, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 806)
- English Speaking Union, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 807)
- Entomology-Grayson, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 808)
- F, General, 1861 (Box 18, Folder 809)
- Faculty Appointments (3 folders), 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 810a-c)
- Faculty Library, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 811)
- Faculty Resignations, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 812)
- Faculty Retirements, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 813)
- Faculty Tenure, 1959-1961 (Box 19, Folder 814)
- Ford Foundation (4 folders), 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 815a-d)
- Health, Education, and Welfare, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 816)
- G, General, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 817)
- Geology-Cooper, 1957-1961 (Box 19, Folder 818)
- Grade Percentages, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 819)
- Guidance and Placement-Cato, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 820)
- H, General, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 821)
- History and Political Science-Jones, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 822)
- Home Economics-Harper, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 823)
- I, General, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 824)
- Inauguration, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 825)
- Industrial Engineering-Manning, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 826)
- Institute of International Education, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 827)
- Invitations, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 828)
- K, General, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 829)
- L, General, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 830)
- Letters of Recommendation, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 831)
- M, General, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 832)
- Mathematics-Hatcher, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 833)
- Mechanical Engineering-Jones, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 834)
- Military-Devine, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 835)
- N, General, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 836)
- National Conference on Higher Education (2 folders), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 837a-b)
- National Science Foundation (2 folders), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 838a-b)
- Nuclear Advisory Board, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 839)
- P, General, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 840)
- Personnel-Evans, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 841)
- Philosophy and Religion-Grover, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 842)
- Physical Education-Younger, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 843)
- President-Newman, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 844)
- Public Relations-McNeil, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 845)
- Questionnaires, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 846)
- R, General, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 847)
- Regional Advisory Council on Nuclear Energy (2 folders), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 848a-b)
- Regional Council on Graduate Education in Agriculture (2 folders), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 849a-b)
- Registrar-Slusher, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 850)
- Roanoke Technical Institute, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 851)
- Rural Sociology-Tate, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 852)
- S, General, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 853)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 854)
- Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 855)
- Southern Regional Education Board (2 folders), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 856a-b)
- Southwest Institute on Institutional Research (2 folders), 1961 (Box 19, Folder 857a-b)
- Speeches, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 858)
- State Board of Education, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 859)
- State Council on Higher Education, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 860)
- Statistics-Harshbarger, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 861)
- Student Activities Committee (2 folders), 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 862a-b)
- Student Affairs, Disciplinary Letters, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 863)
- Student Affairs, Foreign Students, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 864)
- Student Life Regulation Committee, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 865)
- T, General, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 866)
- U, General, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 867)
- U.S. Naval Weapons Lab, Dahlgren, VA, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 868)
- U.S. Steel Foundation Fellowship, 1959-1961 (Box 20, Folder 869)
- Veterinary Science (Box 20, Folder 870)
- Virginia Education Association, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 871)
- Virginia Farm Bureau, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 872)
- Vocational Education-Sanders, 1958-1961 (Box 20, Folder 873)
- W, General, 1959-1961 (Box 20, Folder 874)
- Wine Awards, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 875)
- YMCA-Payne, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 876)
- A, General, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 877)
- Agricultural Experiment Station-Young, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 878)
- Animal Husbandry-Litton, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 879)
- Athletic Council, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 880)
- Board Resolutions, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 881)
- Budget Material (2 folders), 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 882a-b)
- Business Administration-Mitchell, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 883)
- Business Manager-Cassell, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 884)
- C, General, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 885)
- Centennial Committee (2 folders), 1962 (Box 20, Folder 886a-b)
- Chemical Engineering-Bull, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 887)
- Chemistry-Krug, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 888)
- Citation Group, 1959-1962 (Box 20, Folder 889)
- Civil Engineering-Morris, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 890)
- Commencement (2 folders), 1962 (Box 20, Folder 891a-b)
- Community Colleges, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 892)
- Congress, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 893)
- Continuing Education-Keller, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 894)
- Co-operative Engineering-Smith, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 895)
- Council on Graduate Schools in the U.S., 1962 (Box 20, Folder 896)
- D, General, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 897)
- Dairy Science-Graf, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 898)
- Danville Branch-Taylor, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 899)
- Director of Development-Fisher, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 900)
- E, General, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 901)
- Economics-Miller, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 902)
- Education Foundation-Hutcheson, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 903)
- Electrical Engineering-Powley, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 904)
- Engineering and Architecture-Whittemore, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 905)
- English-Peacock, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 906)
- Engineering Mechanics-Pletta, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 907)
- Entomology-Grayson, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 908)
- F, General, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 909)
- Faculty Applications, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 910)
- Faculty Appointments, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 911)
- Faculty Merit Increases, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 912)
- Faculty Promotions, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 913)
- Faculty Resignations, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 914)
- Faculty Retirements, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 915)
- Field Trip Letters, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 916)
- Forestry and Wildlife-Hosner, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 917)
- G, General, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 918)
- Geological Sciences-Cooper, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 919)
- Grade Percentages, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 920)
- Guidance and Placement-Cato, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 921)
- H, General, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 922)
- Health, Education, and Welfare, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 923)
- History and Political Science-Jones, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 924)
- Home Economics-Harper, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 925)
- Horticulture-Judkins, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 926)
- I, General, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 927)
- Industrial Engineering-Manning, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 928)
- Institute of International Education, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 929)
- Invitations, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 930)
- L, General, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 931)
- Langley Field, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 932)
- M, General, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 933)
- Mechanical Engineering-Jones, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 934)
- Military-Schewe, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 935)
- N, General, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 936)
- National Education Association, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 937)
- National science Foundation (3 folders), 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 938a-c)
- O, General, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 939)
- P, General, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 940)
- Personnel-Evans, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 941)
- Physics-Jacobs, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 942)
- President-Hahn, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 943)
- President-Newman (2 folders), 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 944a-b)
- Questionnaires, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 945)
- Registrar-Slusher, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 946)
- Radford College, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 947)
- Roanoke Technical Institute, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 948)
- Science and General Studies, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 949)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (2 folders), 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 950a-b)
- Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 951)
- Southern Interstate Nuclear Board (2 folders), 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 952a-b)
- Southern Regional Education Board (2 folders), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 953a-b)
- Space Radiation Effects Lab, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 954)
- State Advisory Committee on Nuclear Energy, 1958-1962 (Box 21, Folder 955)
- State Board of Education, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 956)
- State Council on Higher Education (2 folders), 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 957a-b)
- Student Activities Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 958)
- Student Affairs-Crawford (3 folders), 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 959a-c)
- Student Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 960)
- Television, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 961)
- V, General, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 962)
- Vocational Education-Sanders, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 963)
- W, General, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 964)
- Water Resources Study, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 965)
- YMCA-Payne, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 966)
- A, General, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 967)
- Academic Council (4 folders), 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 968a-d)
- Accreditation, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 969)
- Admissions-Ferrier, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 970)
- Agricultural Extension Service-Daughtrey, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 971)
- Agriculture-Bell, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 972)
- Atomic Energy Commission, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 973)
- Board of Visitors, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 974)
- Conference of Southern Graduate Deans, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 975)
- Education Foundation-Furr, 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 976)
- Engineering and Architecture-Whittemore, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 977)
- Geological Science-Cooper, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 978)
- Graduate Committee (2 folders), 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 979a-b)
- Health, Education, and Welfare, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 980)
- Horticulture-Judkins, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 981)
- Library-Shirk, 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 982)
- Mathematics, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 983)
- Mechanical Engineering-Jones, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 984)
- Military-Schewe, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 985)
- National Education Association, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 986)
- National Science Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 987)
- Plant Pathology and Physiology-Wingard, 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 988)
- President-Hahn, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 989)
- Salary Listings (2 folders), 1959-1963 (Box 22, Folder 990a-b)
- Southern Interstate Nuclear Board, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 991)
- Southern Regional Education Board, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 992)
- State Council of Higher Education, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 993)
- Statistics-Harshbarger, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 994)
- Student Activities Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 995)
- Virginia Associated Research Center, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 996)
- YMCA, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 997)
- NDEA, 1958-1964
  - NDEA, Actual and Estimated Operation Costs, 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 998)
  - NDEA, Actual and Estimated Operation Costs, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 999)
  - NDEA, Actual and Estimated Operation Costs, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 1000)
  - NDEA, Actual and Estimated Operation Costs (2 folders), 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 1001a-b)
  - NDEA, Actual and Estimated Operation Costs (2 folders), 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 1002a-b)
  - NDEA, Fellowship Program, Applications and Approvals, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 1003)
  - NDEA, Fellowship Program, Applications and Approvals, 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 1004)
  - NDEA, Fellowship Program, Applications and Approvals, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 1005)
  - NDEA, Fellowship Program, Applications and Approvals, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 1006)
  - NDEA, Fellowship Program, Applications and Approvals, 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 1007)
  - NDEA Fellowship Program, General, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 1008)
  - NDEA Fellowship Program, General (2 folders), 1959 (Box 23, Folder 1009a-b)
  - NDEA Fellowship Program, General (2 folders), 1959-1961 (Box 23, Folder 1010a-b)
  - NDEA Fellowship Program, General, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 1011)
  - NDEA Fellowship Program, General, 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 1012)
  - NDEA Fellowship Program, General, 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 1013)
  - NDEA, Fellowship Program, Questionnaires, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 1014)
  - NDEA, Refunds, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 1015)
- ORINS, 1945-1971
  - ORINS, Application Forms, 1952-1955 (Box 23, Folder 1016)
  - ORINS, By-Laws, Employee Guidelines, and Activity Reports, 1947-1948 (Box 23, Folder 1017)
  - ORINS, Correspondence, General, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 1018)
  - ORINS, Correspondence, General, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 1019)
  - ORINS, Correspondence, General, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 1020)
  - ORINS, Correspondence, General, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 1021)
  - ORINS, Correspondence, General, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 1022)
  - ORINS, Correspondence, General, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 1023)
  - ORINS, Correspondence, General, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 1024)
  - ORINS, Correspondence, General, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 1025)
  - ORINS, Correspondence, General, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 1026)
  - ORINS, Correspondence, General, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 1027)
  - ORINS, Correspondence, General, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 1028)
  - ORINS, Executive Director-Pollard, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 1029)
  - ORINS, Executive Director-Pollard, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 1030)
  - ORINS, Executive Director-Pollard (2 folders), 1951 (Box 23, Folder 1031a-b)
  - ORINS, Executive Director-Pollard (2 folders), 1952 (Box 23, Folder 1032a-b)
  - ORINS, Executive Director-Pollard, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 1033)
  - ORINS, Executive Director-Pollard, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 1034)
  - ORINS, Executive Director-Pollard, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 1035)
  - ORINS, Executive Director-Pollard, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 1036)
  - ORINS, Executive Director-Pollard, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 1037)
  - ORINS, Executive Director-Pollard, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 1038)
  - ORINS, Executive Director-Pollard, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 1039)
  - ORINS, Executive Director-Pollard, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 1040)
  - ORINS, Meetings (2 folders), 1947-1950 (Box 23, Folder 1041a-b)
  - ORINS, Meetings, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 1042)
  - ORINS, Meetings (2 folders), 1952 (Box 23, Folder 1043a-b)
  - ORINS, Meetings, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 1044)
  - ORINS, Meetings, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 1045)
  - ORINS, Meetings, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 1046)
  - ORINS, Meetings, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 1047)
  - ORINS, Meetings (2 folders), 1957 (Box 24, Folder 1048a-b)
  - ORINS, Meetings (2 folders), 1958 (Box 24, Folder 1049a-b)
  - ORINS, Meetings (2 folders), 1959 (Box 24, Folder 1050a-b)
  - ORINS, Meetings (2 folders), 1960 (Box 24, Folder 1051a-b)
  - ORINS, Meetings (2 folders), 1961 (Box 24, Folder 1052a-b)
  - ORINS, Meetings, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 1053)
  - ORINS, Newsletters, 1949-1961 (Box 24, Folder 1054)
  - ORINS, Patent Policy, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 1055)
  - ORINS, Petition to the President of the United States, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 1056)
  - ORINS, Project Proposals and Authorization Forms, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 1057)
  - ORINS, Radioactive Isotopes-Obenshain, 1947-1949 (Box 24, Folder 1058)
  - ORINS, University Relations, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 1059)
  - ORINS, University Relations, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 1060)
  - ORINS, University Relations, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 1061)
  - ORINS, University Relations, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 1062)
  - ORINS, University Relations, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 1063)
  - ORINS, University Relations, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 1064)
  - ORINS, University Relations, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 1065)
  - ORINS, University Relations, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 1066)
  - ORINS, University Relations, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 1067)
  - ORINS, University Relations, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 1068)